Resume 2/3/21, 7:56 AM

# PATRICIA ATTAH DATA SCIENTIST

## **Summary**

Current graduate student in data scientist with a major in machine learning a statistical background including understanding of hypothesis testing, confidence intervals PCA, LDA and time series and experience with python, R, SAS and SQL. Applied knowledge of data processing, data mining and machine learning algorithms to solve practical business problems and find data driven solutions to increase efficiency. Some machine learning methods I have applied include classification, clustering, regression and neural networks.

# **Employment**

Jacobs Engineering Structural Designer Feb. 2019

Dallas Texas Feb. 2019 to Current. Feb. 2019 to Current

Design of structural building framework, substructure and superstructure. Elements include foundation, framework and roof. I used critical thinking to ensure that the design is adequate. Applied problem solving skills to issues as they arose. Developed deep understanding of software to produce adequate results and paid attention to detail to complete tasks on time and within budget.

## **Projects**

# Correlation between heart disease and certain biomedical traits

Aug. 2020 to Sept. 2020

machine learning classification model that uses several different algorithms tons which best predicts the outcome of heartsease.

#### **Housing Price Prediction**

June 2020 to July 2020

using regression to create a predictive model for house price prediction.

### Life Expectancy Predictive model Sept. 2020 to Oct. 2020

Creation of predictive model for the life expectancy with regression using various socioeconomic factors.

Records database design

Oct. 2020 to Oct. 2020

Relational database design using SQL Stock Prediction ARIMA Vs I STM

Oct. 2020 to Dec. 2020

Comparison of neural network to machine learning algorithms for prediction of stock using the LSTM and ARIMA models.

#### **Contact**

trishattah@gmail.com

• https://github.com/trishattah/SB-DataScience-Track

**2147808010** 

## **Education**

SMU May 2020 to Current Masters Data Science 2021

Spring Jan. 2020 to Dec. board 2020

Certificate Data science 2020

University of May 2016 to Texas Arlington Dec. 2018 Masters Civil Engineering 2018

## **Skills**

Machine Learning Data Visualisation Big Data Data Mining Problem solving Python SAS R

https://resume.creddle.io/